

**Frontend Developer** 

#### **ADDRESS**

Calle 15 # 9-36

### CONTACT

**+57 3044766419** 

- wildsrincon.netlify.app
- wildsrincon.developer@gmail.com
- **3 01 June 1980**
- **o** wildsrincon
- wildsrincon
- in wildsrincon
- f wrstudioweb

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Scrum Fundamentals** Certified (SFC)

June 2021

ScrumStudy Mexico **EFSET English** 

Certificate 49/100 (B1 November 2020 Intermediate)

**EF SET** 

For more information, check out

Cousera Bootstrap

**Professional Web** 

May **Development** 2020

CodigoFacilito

For more information, check out

rxresu.me

**Javascript** 

June **Professional** 2020 CodigoFacilito

For more information, check out

rxresu.me

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: **Bootstrap 4** 

June 2020

The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

For more information, check out

Cousera Bootstrap

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** B1 Level

**Spanish** Native

HOBBIES **Football** 

**Travelling** 

**Watching TV** 

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Full Stack Web Developer focused on JavaScript technologies. I'm a web developer with more than 5+ years of experience developing websites with HTML, CSS and JavaScript also with WordPress CMS, and web apps with ReactJS and Angular frameworks and services (REST API). I consider myself a technology and learning enthusiast. Currently, in order to improve my skills, I am focusing on new technologies based in cloud technologies and Devops culture.

### **SKILLS**

**Javascript** React Intermediate Intermediate Node JS **Angular** Intermediate Novice My Sql **Bootstrap** Intermediate Intermediate

HTML **CSS and Preprocessors** 

Advanced Advanced **Wordpress Devops** Intermediate Novice **Bash** Linux

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Intermediate

### Alcaldía de Barranquilla Frontend Developer

Development of an interface for an institutional management follow-up

Intermediate

application for the planning secretary of the district of Barranquilla.

- Component and interface development with React JS
- Consumption of microservices generated to visualize the data in the database
- Development of administrative dashboard to visualize data and reports The project achieved traceability of the information because previously the information was received through excel files, which made that at the time of reporting the information had errors and it was very difficult to unify that information to generate reports to the different control entities. Tech-stack: ReactJS, Material UI, JSON, REST API, JavaScript.

### Sempli

Frontend Developer

(September 2020 - October 2020)

(February 2021 - July 2021)

With this model, the company was able to improve by 60% through data analysis to find less financially risky candidates when granting a new loan. Tropicode Team Capstone project to develop a \_rst solution approach in Machine Learning to Sempli company. \*\*Experience: data cleaning/treatment with Anaconda and Python, landing page layout design, and practicing infrastructure deployment as code with SAM aws services.

## **WR Studio Web**

Freelance Web Developer

- Development Web sites, web-apps and mobile application
- Management and support of websites (Content Management System, Availability of portals)
- · Customer support.

### Safe SAS Frontend Developer

(January 2016 - December 2016)

(January 2013 - December 2019)

- Development Web sites, web-apps and mobile application
- Management and support of websites (Content Managers, Availability of portals)
- Customer support.

# **EDUCATION**

### **Holberton School, Colombia Bootcamp** Advanced Program Web Stack

(January 2020 - July 2021)

Advanced Program Web Stack, Apr 2021 - Present

· Advanced program in Web Stack programming, Build dynamic and responsive web applications from the database to the user interactions.

Foundations Program, Jan 2020 - Nov 2020

 Software Engineering Specialty and achieved a much more thorough education in the underlying theory, concepts, and science behind more complex programming.

# SENA, Barranquilla, Colombia

**Higher School** Networks Administration Technology

(January 2003 - June 2006)

Acquired skills in configuring active network equipment, general data networking topics and computer network administration.

# **PROJECTS**

**Github Battle** https://github-battle-wr.netlify.app/ (December 2020 - December 2020)

Project build with React and React Router, consuming API Github and deploy production and CI/CD with Netlify. Funny game of battle Github profiles.

# **Adopt Me**

https://adopt-me-wr.vercel.app

(August 2020 - July 2021)

Adopt Me , a free and open-source app built in with React JS works for you. A few of the important features that make it awesome are API Consuming, the app is connected to an animal adoption service that works only for the USA. For more information, check out **rxresu.me** 

# **Angular Weather App**

https://weather-app-66cf5.web.app/

(June 2020 - July 2021)

Angular App built in Angular 9, API consuming Open Weather API, weather forecast for next five days, use geolocation service for show your location.

# Robofriends

https://robofriends-wr.netlify.app/

(November 2019 - July 2021)

React App robot search engine, use API Robohash for the import data.